Please give me high marks for the DVD, etc.
Here we go. Upokami.
This time, I'll be talking with Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda,
Morning Musume。 23, and Reina Yokoyama from Morning Musume。
This program will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
We will show you our recording, rehearsal, and other production processes.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Sakura Oda, will be talking about Morning Musume。' 23 dressed up for Halloween for the first time.
It was about two or three days before Halloween, the day we were to meet our fans at the benefit event,
I dressed up as a black cat and gave a talk,
Geita-chan Yumi told me that her favorite senior member of Morning Musume。 I knew that Geitaiko Yumi had always told me that her favorite senior member of Morning Musume,
I don't know if it was because she was wearing an unusual outfit, but she was being photographed in a way that I really didn't notice.
The pace was really fast and furious,
So, since Ako-chan was eating her favorite plum candy,
I said, "Ako-chan, Ako-chan, Torikko is Torikko," and she said, "I'll give you all of them.
She was like me.
Ako-chan is quite crisp, so I had an image of her as always being cool,
But she is more affectionate than I thought,
Her love is amazing, isn't it?
She was cute.
The two members of the 17th term have been showing more of their true selves recently,
Haruka Inoue also brought sweets like this on the day of the Halloween talk session,
She went around to each of the senior members' booths with candy like this,
When I asked her if she was going to give it to me, she said "Yes. I asked her if she was going to give it to me, and she said yes.
She was so cute.
I would like to show that kind of thing to my fans more and more.
Yes, and I, Yokoyama, have been posting a lot of videos on SNS lately.
I tend to post only pictures on social networking sites like Instagram, but I want people to see me in action.
But recently I've been thinking that I want people to see me in action as well.
So I have started to take and post not only photos, but also videos of me in action. I have started taking and posting not only photos, but also videos of me in action.
I'm glad that many people are happy with the results, so I'd like to keep doing it.
I would like to continue to do so in the future.
I'd like to continue to post more and more of our videos to our fans.
Let's start with this video.
Morning Musume。 23 73rd single jacket shooting making
It was released on October 25th!
Morning Musume。 23 73rd single jacket shoot!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto, Japan. I am 17 years old and a high school sophomore from Kyoto, Japan.
I am 15 years old, a junior high school student from Shizuoka, Japan. I am a junior high school student, 15 years old, from Shizuoka, Japan.
I am 15 years old, a junior high school student, from Shizuoka, Japan. I am a junior high school student, 15 years old, from Shizuoka, Japan.
Teosilon?
Yes, Korean.
Yes, you can do the colors by hand like this.
Nice!
The wind was amazing. I don't have anything like this, so I'm looking forward to it.
I look forward to working with you.
I was so nervous.
It's like this. Nice to meet you.
Excuse me.
Sometimes you smile. Sometimes you smile.
Smile.
Okay. - Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Okay, well, cool, I want to do some stuff.
Here we go, three, first, here we go, two, yo, straight
last, yo, both hands, both hands, yes, good, stick, yo, cool, cool, cool
Yo, here we go. Yo, let's go!
[ED]
Smile, smile, smile. I want a lot of things.
Smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile, smile.
Smile, smile, call, call, call, call, call.
Smiles, calls for more smiles, more calls for more calls for more smiles.
Smiles, calls, calls, calls, calls, calls, calls, calls, calls.
They're all cute.
Everybody's cute
Today, after 10 years, Moni Musume. I was so full of energy to see them again.
I'm actually going to sing a song at karaoke with Moni Musume. I sing songs.
So I sang some small karaoke songs,
I never thought that this summer I would be asked to do a photo shoot for Moni Musume。 I was asked to do a photo shoot for "Moni Musume,
I've been back from New York since the day before yesterday, and I was really looking forward to it.
Compared to 10 years ago, the new members now,
I feel a different kind of energy.
The new Moni Musume. The wind of "Moni Musume,
I also feel the energy and brilliance of these karaoke members once again.
I took a lot of pictures with the concept of this time.
I hope that the fans of Moni Musume. I hope the fans of Moni Musume,
I hope that the fans of MoniMusume。
I hope the next time we meet will not be until 10 years from now.
Please let us make another album. I am looking forward to it.
Thank you so much for your time today.
I was there 10 years ago, so this was my second time to have Leslie Key take pictures of me, and I had told him that morning that I was looking forward to it, saying that the fact that he was at this site today meant that this was the best site in Asia.
The moment I saw the group arrangement, I remembered how I felt 10 years ago, and I thought that this was Leslie Kee's arrangement.
I was really impressed with the poses and the angles of the legs, and when I looked at the finished photos again, I thought how beautiful the photos looked.
I was also impressed by the unexpected speed at which the shooting progressed. I thought that this was the speed of Lesliquie's shooting, and at first I couldn't hide my confusion. I thought, "Oh my God, we've already finished shooting.
I had never met them before, so I knew how they were going to proceed like this, and when I saw the finished product, I really felt that they had thought about the angles at which each member looked beautiful, and everyone looked great. I was really happy to have Leslie Kee's picture taken of me. I had never met them before, so I learned about the process of the event, and I was really impressed by the angles at which the members looked beautiful. I was really happy to have Leslie Key take my picture.
We were watching the making of the film, and I thought that Yumi Shirayumi's confusion was all over her face.
She was so cute, wasn't she?
I watched it with a big smile on my face.
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
We were guessing each other, weren't we?
Yes, we did. "Is this one okay? You were focusing with a look that said, "Is this the right one?
You have a nice bend in your back.
It's true.
It's really good looking.
Is this in focus? He looked like he was about right.
Mr. Leslie Key is bending with you, isn't he?
Yes, we're all crooked together.
That's because I'm a beginner.
She was really cute in that way, too.
It was cute.
It was a lot of fun.
It was a good time.
Well, that's all for now. 2373rd single jacket photo shoot.
Amazing, amazing, amazing!
It all just ends with that one lie.
Morning Musume。 23 Super Fever!
Now on sale!
Thank you for your work
Next is here. Tea Horse Ruri Hiromoto's hair arrangement
Here is Ruri Hiromoto's hair arrangement. This time, she shows us a braided arrangement. Please take a look.
My name is Ruri Hiromoto from Ocha-no-Ma.
Today I would like to introduce Ruri Hiromoto's braided hair arrangement.
There are two types of braided hair arrangement: back braiding and front braiding,There are two types of braiding arrangements: back braiding and front braiding,
I change them according to the mood of the outfit at the time,
The front braid is used for a soft and fluffy look, or when you are wearing cute clothes like today.
I use the back knitting when I want to make a tight knit or when I want to make a tight knit for a performance,
In this article, I would like to show you the difference between the outer and inner knitting on the right and left sides.
Let's start with the front knitting.
Let's start from this side,
First, take a little bit from the top.
When I divide the front braid into three parts, I cover the top part of the braid like a normal braid.
Then, the third time, I take a little bit of the front side, and this time, I put it over the front side and take a little bit of the back side.
Then, pull this front side again, and add it here again.
And now, the back side is placed on top like this, which is the outer knitting.
And at this time, I'm moving the back side more and more.
If you take everything from the front to the back, it will look like it's peeling off.
It tends to look peeled off.
It's like this area is pulled too much.
That's why I took the braid from the back until the middle of the braid.
When it comes to the bottom, you can gently cover it.
It makes it look like there's a good amount of hair.
I think it makes it look like there's a good amount of hair.
I think it gives a nice finish.
And when I'm braiding...
I take out all the hairs that I just took out.
If you go too far to the back when you're braiding
If you go too far back, you won't be able to see the braid on the front side.
So you need to keep it close to the face.
and the braid should be right behind the ear.
It's a good idea to do it while being conscious of it.
You can do it however you like.
The last part of the braid tends to be a little bit loose. And the last part tends to be a little bit loose.
I think it tends to go down a little bit here.
I think it's better to take it all off in one go at the end.
The finished product will be very beautiful.
I'm fine with taking it all off in one go.
It's better that way.
It looks more beautiful.
And then, braid from here to the bottom, like this.
Like this. It's cute if you braid all the way to the bottom.
It's cute if you braid all the way to the bottom, but if you curl the braid in advance like this, it's also pretty cute if you leave the bottom part curled and tie it.
And from here, depending on the day, you can pull it out a little bit at a time.
When you pull it out, you can see the main part of the braid.
When you pull out the braid, it's better to pull out the braid at the back of the braid.
It's cuter if you pull the braid out.
It looks fluffier if you pull this braid.
This is the front braid.
Next, I'd like to braid this side in the back.
When I wore the white and member-color costumes that I've been wearing since before I made my major debut, I used to braid my hair into a twin hairstyle, right?
I used to do this back braid, but what's different is that I divided it into three parts.
I used to do this backstitching, but what's different is that I divided it into three sections.
And then I'm going to do the same thing, starting from the front and working my way down.
Take it from here and put it down.
Take it from here and put it on the bottom.
This is the difference between back knitting and front knitting.
And the point to be careful is the same as before,
The back knitting is the one you need to pay attention to,
The back braid looks more neat and clean.
If it goes too far back, it will not look good from the front,
It's more cute to have the braid all the way down here,
That's a point you should be aware of when you're back braiding. That is a point that we should be aware of when knitting in the back.
Yes, I am aware of that. This is back knitting.
In the front knitting, the knit is in the middle, but in the back knitting, the knit is on the front...oh, no, it's not.
The knitting is on the top. It goes on and on and on and on.
The difference is that when you knit the reverse side, you pull out the whole of the knitting,
I personally think it's prettier to pull out a little bundle of hair thinly when it's knitted backwards.
And this one is more like a braid, isn't it? The braid is showing.
I think it's easier to make it fluffy here.
So, the braid is done!
As I said at the beginning, this side is the front braid, and this side is the back braid.
Well, when it's braided in the front, it gives a fluffy look, so it looks cute when you wear a cute outfit like this,
On the other hand, when you wear show pants, or in summer....
On the other hand, when you wear a sleeveless shirt, a white shirt like "The Natsu" and jeans, this is more suitable.
I think it looks tighter, so please try it depending on your needs.
You can also try tying it here and then curling it to make a bear or something, so please experiment!
That's all for now, this is Reiri Hiramoto at tea time.
You taught me in a way that was very easy to understand.
I really enjoyed watching it, thinking about how I've been thinking about it.
You were really good at it!
You were very good.
You were so beautiful, and you knitted so easily.
I have to knit and knit again, and again, and again, and again, to make it beautiful.
I was watching and thinking, "You're really good at this!
I, Sakura Oda, also like to arrange my hair.
I cut my hair to this length about two months ago.
I just couldn't do it anymore.
That's right.
I'm looking at this right now, and I was thinking that I'd like to arrange it for someone else.
I wonder if you could lend me your long hair.
What's that? What's that?
Parents?
Can I borrow it sometime?
Sure.
Thank you very much.
She's really pretty.
And we have really similar hair.
The members of the Halo Project are really something.
I do it myself.
There are girls with all kinds of artistry and all kinds of hair textures.
Lately, there's been a lot of girls who are fans.
There are more and more girls who are cute, and I think they're trying to be cute.
I'm learning a lot from them.
I learned a lot.
I think it was that kind of time.
This is Ruri Hiromoto's hair arrangement for the tea ceremony.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and Morning Musume。 23's Reina Yokoyama is presenting this up-dated paper. Here is the next one.
Juice! Juice! Bon Voyage! The Miracle of Thoughts! Juice! Juice! Juice!
Bon Voyage! Juice! Juice's latest album, Bon Voyage! Watch Kazuka Arisawa's violin recording session.
Are you okay with the headphones? I'm fine.
Now we have to fight against humidity. Fighting with humidity?
I want it to sound fun for the listeners. That's about it.
I'm listening to it now.
I feel like I'm listening more carefully than before.
So it's not so much that I'm enjoying it, but that I'm listening to it very carefully.
I don't know if I'd call it serious.I'm not sure if I'd call it serious.
I don't know, it just sounded like...
It was more like...
Rough.
I don't know how to say "rougher".
It's more like "Alisa".
It's not like "de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de
I think it's more like "de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de
I thought it would be more playful at all like
Just dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah
It doesn't matter what you do.
I don't know.
Can I make it more expressive?
Okay, I'll do it.
And, and, and, and, and...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The part where he says "in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in...
I can make it even more expressive.
You can say "de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de.
It's like an electric guitar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just listen to it and do it.
Just that feeling.
Just a thought that comes to you in the moment.
Yes.
Ending
I don't think it's so bad now.
I think it's not so bad now, even if it's a fast sell.
I wish it came out betterI wish it came out better.
I really feel like it's going to flow there and stuff.
I feel like it's going to flow there, too.
I think it would be great if we could get that part right.
Music
Okay.
Yes.
Can I take a second shot?
Okay.
Music
♪♪
It's hard to get my sound right.
Yes, it is.
It's hard.
Well, I think Afresh itself is totally fine.
Yes, it is.
Let's try one more time.
Yes.
♪♪
Thank you for your hard work.
me
Right.
I'm just like you, theater.
I was in a state of confusion.
Can I try to match the third one with the third one?
You mean another one?
Yes, can I try the third violin too?
Okay, okay, okay, can I try one?Okay, okay, okay. Can we do it once?
Can I do the first one now, and the second one while you're doing it?
Yes, please.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, let's do a little bit more of that.
Okay.
Did you change it?
Oh, um...
Oh, wow.
D and...
Play it on fourth.
On the do.
I changed it a little bit from playing it on the slide to playing it on the slide.
Oh, that's it?
No, but that was good.
I'll go with that one.
Let's listen to that one.
blink gall-in at the name place
is a memorable place with a studio in Sendai.
Yes. Is this how it's going to be?
Yes, sir.
Thanks, good night!
Thank you very much.
You were so cool! I can't play any instruments, so I don't know much about it.
I don't know much about it, but with a voice, you can stop it, can't you? Violin is an instrument that keeps making sounds, not stopping while playing.
So you can keep playing the rhythm that we're usually so conscious of, and then suddenly stop, or move at a speed that makes it sound like you've stopped.
I thought it was amazing, and I was coming up with my own ideas one after another.
I was thinking about how the three-eyed kabuseh is done. I'm really glad that Hello! Project has such a cool kid.
I was an alto saxophonist, so I had to adjust the pitch by the way I moved my mouth.
I was an alto saxophone player, so I had to adjust the pitch by the way I moved my mouth. It's an instrument like singing, where you can make changes with your mouth and throat, but it's really cool how you can add desire with your hands and other parts.
I think it's really cool that you can add greed to your playing with your hands and other parts of your body, and I also thought that Kazuka Arisawa must really like playing.
I also thought that Kazuka Arisawa must really like performing, and I thought it was really cool that a girl who does what she loves to do is so cool.
That's all for JuiceJuice Bon Voyage, the miracle of my heart, Kazuka Arisawa's Bionin Recording.
Let's work together!
It's time for Sakura Oda and Rena Yokoyama to say goodbye!
Well, we've seen various videos this time too, but I still think Arisao Kazuka's violin is really cool and I want to listen to it forever.
I want to listen to it forever... as someone who also plays an instrument like that...
I felt like I wanted to listen to it forever... as someone who plays a musical instrument myself, I felt like she must have practiced a lot, she seemed to be having a lot of fun, she really likes playing the instrument... I felt so many emotions.
I, Sakura Oda, was in the making of the shooting for the jacket of our CD.
When Leslie Kee took pictures of me before, I had an all-back hair style with a nice make-up and I looked so sharp.
I was 14 years old and now I'm 24.
I was so happy to see the members in poses that I'm not used to seeing.
I was also grateful to be able to see the members in poses that I'm not used to seeing, and to see the hard work they put in.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see!
This time upcami is with Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and Morning Musume。 23 and Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume。
Farewell!
Next time on Up-Kami: Yoshikazu Miyamoto, the making of Bambi Bambi's music video shoot, and Morning Musume,
Morning Musume。 23's recording of "Wake up call wake up time" will be shown in the next issue.
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel.